{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Play \u0026 Swing Set Installation Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40231/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40231,"taskName":"Outdoor Play Equipment - Install","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Outdoor Play Equipment","xmTaskDescriptor":"Play \u0026 Swing Set Installation Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1105,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Outdoor Equipment playsets playhouses playground","textMessagingName":"Play Equipment","rolloverLongDesc":"This category is for the professional installation of play systems. To assemble play equipment purchased elsewhere, search under handyman.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes climbing, forts, jungle gyms, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Outdoor Play Equipment.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Play \u0026 Swing Set Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Playground \u0026 Outdoor Equipment","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":54,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Outdoor Play Equipment Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Play Equipment - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Outdoor Play Equipment Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Play-Equipment-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Play \u0026 Swing Set Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Outdoor,Equipment,playsets,playhouses,playground,Play,swingsets,set,swing","emcCategoryOid":-12053,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":538,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40231/":{"taskOID":40231,"originalTaskOID":40231,"setID":538,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4930,"questionDisplayText":"Children's ages","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are the ages of the children who will be using this equipment?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":400,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"2-5 years","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":543,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6-11 years","answerDisplayText":"6-11 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":344,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"12-plus years","answerDisplayText":"12-plus years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4931,"questionDisplayText":"Number using equipment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many children will be using the equipment at the same time?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":293,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1-3","answerDisplayText":"1-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":490,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-8","answerDisplayText":"4-8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":567,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"9-15","answerDisplayText":"9-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":356,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16-25","answerDisplayText":"16-25","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":423,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"26-plus","answerDisplayText":"26-plus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4934,"questionDisplayText":"Special features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features/activities would you like included? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6225,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Swings/gliders","answerDisplayText":"Swings/gliders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3909,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Monkey bars","answerDisplayText":"Monkey bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ladders","answerDisplayText":"Ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4762,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Poles","answerDisplayText":"Poles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4724,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Platform levels","answerDisplayText":"Platform levels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5423,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ropes","answerDisplayText":"Ropes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5414,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof/canopy","answerDisplayText":"Roof/canopy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6481,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Trapezes","answerDisplayText":"Trapezes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5353,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Rides","answerDisplayText":"Rides","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5367,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Rock climbing wall","answerDisplayText":"Rock climbing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5477,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Sand box","answerDisplayText":"Sand box","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4930,"questionDisplayText":"Children's ages","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What are the ages of the children who will be using this equipment?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":400,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"2-5 years","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":543,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6-11 years","answerDisplayText":"6-11 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":344,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"12-plus years","answerDisplayText":"12-plus years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":400,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"2-5 years","answerDisplayText":"2-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":543,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"6-11 years","answerDisplayText":"6-11 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":344,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"12-plus years","answerDisplayText":"12-plus years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4931,"questionDisplayText":"Number using equipment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many children will be using the equipment at the same time?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":293,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1-3","answerDisplayText":"1-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":490,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-8","answerDisplayText":"4-8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":567,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"9-15","answerDisplayText":"9-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":356,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16-25","answerDisplayText":"16-25","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":423,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"26-plus","answerDisplayText":"26-plus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":293,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1-3","answerDisplayText":"1-3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":490,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-8","answerDisplayText":"4-8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":567,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"9-15","answerDisplayText":"9-15","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":356,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"16-25","answerDisplayText":"16-25","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":423,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"26-plus","answerDisplayText":"26-plus","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4934,"questionDisplayText":"Special features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features/activities would you like included? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6225,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Swings/gliders","answerDisplayText":"Swings/gliders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3909,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Monkey bars","answerDisplayText":"Monkey bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ladders","answerDisplayText":"Ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4762,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Poles","answerDisplayText":"Poles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4724,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Platform levels","answerDisplayText":"Platform levels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5423,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ropes","answerDisplayText":"Ropes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5414,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof/canopy","answerDisplayText":"Roof/canopy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6481,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Trapezes","answerDisplayText":"Trapezes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5353,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Rides","answerDisplayText":"Rides","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5367,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Rock climbing wall","answerDisplayText":"Rock climbing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5477,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Sand box","answerDisplayText":"Sand box","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6225,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Swings/gliders","answerDisplayText":"Swings/gliders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3909,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Monkey bars","answerDisplayText":"Monkey bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ladders","answerDisplayText":"Ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4762,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Poles","answerDisplayText":"Poles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4724,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Platform levels","answerDisplayText":"Platform levels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5423,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ropes","answerDisplayText":"Ropes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5414,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof/canopy","answerDisplayText":"Roof/canopy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6481,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Trapezes","answerDisplayText":"Trapezes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5353,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Rides","answerDisplayText":"Rides","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5367,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Rock climbing wall","answerDisplayText":"Rock climbing wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5477,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Sand box","answerDisplayText":"Sand box","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":40001,"questionDisplayText":"Materials Provided by Homeowner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will you provide materials for this request?","shortQuestionText":"Homeowner to provide materials?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}